Hi, in this lesson, I will show you how to setup in sort of the Jitter.
If you visit the inside side and click on download button, or you just open the resource
and share it with this lesson, you will go to this page.
And website suggests you download the quarter-sore, especially for your platform, so it will
be auto-detected, or you can click download more options and choose your platform manually.
I will download it for @OCLICOM, and also you are able to install extension of the wind
surf to your quarter-detors, but it suggests you to use the quarter-detors itself not plugin.
So, I will click download, download it for @OCLICOM, I will wait, now it's downloaded, I just
started, and it will take 5/10 seconds just to install an application.
Okay, I can close it, and now I can run the wind surf.
So, when you run it, you will see the onboarding screen, so we just click get started, and
you will have 3 options.
You can import, so if you previously use the Visual Studio Code or quarter-sore, you can import
all the settings and all the extension from these detors.
So, or you can start from fresh, so if you don't want to import anything, I will import
everything from Visual Studio Code, I will import settings and extensions, and you can
choose the team you like, or you can try to import it from the quarter-detors you used
before.
Then you need to create an account, I will click login, because I already have an account,
but you will see this screen, so you will need to enter your credentials, or you can just
sign up with Google or GitHub.
After you end up all again to the wind surf, you can open it, okay, you see high-dimensional
that surf, okay, and everything is opened, so, and now there is one important moment, it's
about zero data retention.
If you want to disable it, you need to go to your profile, on the website, and you can
click on settings, and right here you will find the privacy, and I recommend you to disable
this telemetry, and then you want to share your data with wind surf, and it won't
train on your data, on your code examples, or just enable the toggle to disable it to
the telemetry.
Okay, let's open the wind surf quarter-detors, so you see, so if you click on wind surf,
right here you will have settings for the wind surf and settings for the editor, so you
can go through it and learn what settings you have, what you can use, right here, and
it's easy to see when you register for wind surf, you have 100 from credits left because
it's your 3L, and there is a date, how much days it will be active, so, a minute left
on the eight days, okay, I hope this lesson was useful for you and see you in the next
Oh, that's one.